"Kiss or Kill"
(Episode 2)
I'm here.
You think you can just walk away?
I'm just here to do business.
There's no need for this.
You bastard.
You dare point a knife at me?
You have a death wish.
Enough!
Stay out of this.
I'm gonna kill him today.
Nobody points a knife at me and lives.
Kill him!
Lead the way.
I have plenty of ways to make him talk.
That won't be necessary.
This guy...
I'll interrogate him.
What do you mean?
You're too heavy-handed.
If you ruin our lead,
it's bad for all of us.
He's my prisoner.
He belongs to Lin.
Where's the interrogation?
I'll take him there.
I suggest you don't cause trouble.
Brother Scorpion, what do we do?
Didn't you hear what the kid said?
Don't cause trouble.
Yes, sir.
He's a tough one.
One more kick and he's done for.
Come on, you interrogate him.
Get out.
Why should I?
You know exactly why.
When it comes to this,
I'm better at it than you.
I'm only giving you half an hour.
Looks like
you've had a rough trip.
You should have expected that.
What I didn't expect is
what exactly you're here for.
To do business, of course.
Is that so?
What else?
As for you,
you look like
a top executive of the Lin Group.
Don't tell me you're the boss.
I guessed right.
Boss Lin.
Is this how you treat your guests?
You're a mercenary.
What kind of business are you here for?
Even mercenaries
want to score big.
Still being a smartass.
I control the routes.
You can test them anytime.
Let me ask you.
Who is your employer?
Or rather,
who is your target?
What if my target is you?
Then before you make a move,
I'll take your life first.
Is that so?
You think I won't?
Because...
Because three years ago,
I saved a life.
All done.
Let's grab a drink tonight.
Keep fooling around.
The military has rules.
I can't join you.
That's why I say,
freedom is the best.
Don't...
Don't kill me!
Who are you?
I'm a photographer.
Someone's chasing me.
At least six of them.
Why are they chasing you?
They're terrorists.
I caught something on camera.
And they spotted me.
Get down!
Three on the left.
Two on the right.
More in the back.
How many did you say were chasing you?
Six.
But two more just showed up.
You sure kept a good count.
I'll push the left.
You cover me. Can you do that?
I think so.
Know how to use it?
I'll try.
You've got some skills.
Right back at you.
Two at ten o'clock.
Two at two o'clock.
You take left, I take right.
Not bad, huh?
Watch out!
I'm sorry.
I was careless.
Two more left.
Behind the oil barrels at ten o'clock.
We're clear.
No.
The gunshots definitely
alerted more of them.
I'm getting you out of here.
Stay awake.
I'm awake.
Just a little tired.
We just met.
At least you should let me know
who you really are.
A combat photographer.
Yeah, right.
Hold on tight.
Who are you, really?
I told you.
A combat photographer.
A combat photographer
doesn't shoot that well.
Let alone kill people.
But that doesn't matter right now.
You need to treat that wound immediately.
Bite down on this.
Bear with it.
Don't move.
The more you cooperate,
the less it'll hurt.
Go check inside.
I'm surprised.
You didn't even make a sound.
I was afraid your hands would shake
and you'd stitch it crooked.
Good technique.
Lots of practice.
You're from the military.
Good eye.
Spending years in war zones,
I've seen a lot.
However,
you're definitely different from them.
How so?
Am I more handsome?
You're more unruly.
A mercenary who works for money
doesn't need rules.
Just a mercenary?
Six years ago,
I was a proper border guard.
Why did you quit?
During a mission once,
intel said
it was a militant stronghold.
But I saw
women and children in the village.
If the airstrike hit,
they would all die.
So you...
You disobeyed orders.
I led my team
and snuck in on foot.
We saved most of them.
But there were still a few
who didn't make it out.
[Discharge order]
You saved those people,
but lost your military status.
Do you regret it?
No regrets.
When we were evacuating,
a kid turned back and smiled at me.
I knew right then
it was worth it.
What if that kid
was also a militant?
You mean
a kid who could barely speak?
You never know.
What on earth have you been through
to make you think like that?
As a combat photographer,
I've documented a lot.
Naturally, I overthink.
If you think so much,
didn't you ever think I might hurt you?
If you were going to hurt me,
you wouldn't have opened fire for me.
Are all photographers as smart as you?
It seems I guessed right.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Ran into a little situation just now.
Minor issue. It's handled.
I have to go.
You still haven't told me.
What's your name?
Just call me A-yang.
Doesn't sound like a real name.
Would you tell me your real name?
I'm...
Nie Chuan.
Let me have this.
No way.
I did save your life, after all.
I deserve some kind of reward.
You'll regret this.
I told you.
You'd regret it.
Regret what?
Regret messing with you three years ago?
Or regret...
falling into your hands now?
I really misjudged you.
You change your tune pretty fast.
Tell me.
How did you misjudge me?
I was blind.
If I had known earlier...
that you were such a big boss...
back then...
I wouldn't have let you go.
Then starting today...
You're staying at my place.
So you agree to hire me?
Boss Lin.
I don't trust your route.
And I trust you even less.
So it's imprisonment?
It's a deal.
A deal?
Then what do I get out of it?
You give me the route.
I keep you alive.
Sounds like I'm getting
the short end of the stick.
You can leave.
I'm not leaving.
Leaving would be a bigger loss.
Originally, it was for the money.
But now...
Things are getting interesting.
Since you want to stay...
Then...
As you wish.
Is this how the Lin family treats its guests?
I did save your life, you know.
It's not bad.
At least you get to sit on the couch.
Is this your place?
So luxurious and comfortable.
Look up.
So direct?
You talk too much.
Guess you didn't get beaten enough.
Easy.
Are you disinfecting or torturing me?
If you're afraid of pain, behave.
You used to be so gentle.
You didn't use to be this annoying.
A-yang.
Or should I say...
Lin Yan.
Finally know your real name.
I'm still Nie Chuan.
Nie Chuan the mercenary?
Or Nie Chuan the guide?
Both.
I'm very honest.
Unlike some people.
So hypocritical.
Got it, Second Uncle. Understood.